# frozen_string_literal: true
# This file should contain all the record creation needed to experiment with
# your app during development.
#
# The data can then be loaded with the rake db:examples (or created alongside
# the db with db:nuke_pave).
#
# Examples:
#
#   cities = City.create([{ name: 'Chicago' }, { name: 'Copenhagen' }])
#   Mayor.create(name: 'Emanuel', city: cities.first)

# %w(antony jeff matt jason).each do |name|
#   email = "#{name}@#{name}.com"
#   next if User.exists? email: email
#   User.create!(email: email,
#                password: 'abc123',
#                password_confirmation: nil)
# end

Question.create!(
  problem: 'What would you have if you had five mango and two bananas in one hand and two mango and four bananas in the other hand?',
  correct: 'Very large hands',
  wrongOne: 'mangos and bananas',
  wrongTwo: 'handful of fruits',
  wrongThree: 'Nothing'
)

Question.create!(
  problem: 'What is the capital of Panama?',
  correct: 'Panama City',
  wrongOne: 'El Panama',
  wrongTwo: 'Pajama',
  wrongThree: 'Banana'
)

Question.create!(
  problem: 'What is the third law of Motion?',
  correct: 'For every action, there is an equal and opposite reaction',
  wrongOne: 'Relationship between force, mass and acceleration',
  wrongTwo: 'Law of Inertia',
  wrongThree: 'Gravity'
)

Question.create!(
  problem: 'What is the first law of Motion?',
  correct: 'Law of Inertia',
  wrongOne: 'Relationship between force, mass and acceleration',
  wrongTwo: 'For every action, there is an equal and opposite reaction',
  wrongThree: 'Gravity'
)

Question.create!(
  problem: 'What is the second law of Motion?',
  correct: 'Relationship between force, mass and acceleration',
  wrongOne: 'For every action, there is an equal and opposite reaction',
  wrongTwo: 'Law of Inertia',
  wrongThree: 'Gravity'
)

Question.create!(
  problem: 'Where do Pineapple grow on?',
  correct: 'Bush',
  wrongOne: 'Tree',
  wrongTwo: 'Ground',
  wrongThree: 'PPAP'
)

Question.create!(
  problem: 'Why did the Mathematician install a knockers on his door?',
  correct: 'For the Nobel Prize',
  wrongOne: 'So people can knock on it',
  wrongTwo: 'It looks good on the door',
  wrongThree: 'He likes it'
)

Question.create!(
  problem: 'How, What, and Where?',
  correct: 'Modeling',
  wrongOne: 'Huh?',
  wrongTwo: 'Right...',
  wrongThree: 'Need more Info'
)

Question.create!(
  problem: 'How did the word, debug, came to be?',
  correct: 'Grace Hopper',
  wrongOne: 'Alexander Russell',
  wrongTwo: 'It was always there',
  wrongThree: 'Dennis Ritchie'
)

Question.create!(
  problem: 'The language C was developed by...',
  correct: 'Both of them',
  wrongOne: 'Neither of them',
  wrongTwo: 'Dennis Ritchie',
  wrongThree: 'Ken Thompson'
)

Question.create!(
  problem: 'Who invented the first computer resembling todays modern machines',
  correct: 'Charles Babbage',
  wrongOne: 'William Oughtred',
  wrongTwo: 'Dennis Ritchie',
  wrongThree: 'Grace Hopper'
)
